This is the early Ministry of Prophet T.B.Joshua
The acts of giving started right at the beginning of his Ministry
As you can see, by the view of the church, this is indeed the early Ministry.
Let's listen to Prophet T.B. Joshua
As many as we are in the congregation,
can we see someone who can say they are the poorest here?
T.B. Joshua asked the congregation; Can we see someone who can say they are the poorest here?
The Early Ministry of Prophet T.B. Joshua
Look at the many people coming out in response to the Man of God's question.
Lets listen to one of them.
I have been suffering since i was young.
I have no job, nothing.
My children are scattered everywhere.
I cried every year.
I even cried this morning before coming to The Synagogue Church.
The woman says that she has been suffering since she was very young.
She has no job, nothing, her children have scattered about and she cries all the time
Take. this is the key to a bus.
The man of God, T.B. Joshua gives the woman the key to a bus.
The Man of God, would have wanted to give her money worth the cost of the bus but the woman
insisted that she wants to go with a bus
She said, she will use it for commercial purposes, as a transportation bus
and this will help her to earn money, by which she and her family could live; Money
for accommodation, her children's School fees and her life's welfare.
Along with the key, this woman was also given a licence and the registration papers for the vehicle,
proof that she is now the proud owner of the bus.
Those who once saw her as a poor woman, will now see her as a blessed child.
This is the first bus that was given to the Man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua in his early Ministry.
It was his first time, ever to own or have a bus.
But instead of using this bus bus for his own personal benefits, he said it is not yet time for me to use a bus.
He gave the bus to the needy.
God's time is the best.
What is your name?
My name is Florence Olawaye.
The suffering was too much,
Even to eat and drink was difficult.
I have been suffering since 15 years
I am a member of Christ Apostolic Church.
What happened to you today?
I was given a key to this bus.
Florence recounts her former life of suffering
She is saying, for the past 15 years, life has been a struggle, even finding means to eat and drink is difficult
but God heard her cry, and through T.B Joshua she was given a key to her own bus.
Watch, as she walks towards the door of her new bus and opens it with the key.
The key she received, as a gift from the Man of God, not only to unlock the door of the vehicle
but open the way for her to start life anew.
Psalms 30 verse 5 says, sorrow may last for a night but joy cometh in the morning
As she sits in her new bus, she sings praises to God, because he has taken over her sorrow
and replaced with joy
We believe, you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched
CLICK HERE, TO SUBSCRIBE, TO WITNESS MORE OF GOD'S POWER AT WORK IN OUR GENERATION TODAY
AND STAY UPTODATE WITH THE LATEST PROPHESIES, DELIVERANCES, SERMONS AND TESTIMONIES
FROM THE SYNAGOGUE CHURCH OF ALL NATIONS.
emmanuel.tv scoan.org facebook.com/tbjministries